chatvibes.com 2011-05-01

# ChatVibes Social Video Chat Privacy Terms

Thank you for reviewing our Privacy Policy. This website, [www.chatvibes.com](http://www.chatvibes.com/) (the "Site") is operated from the United States. Your privacy is important to us. It is our policy to protect your Personal Information (as defined below) and to use it only in accordance with this Privacy Policy

ChatVibes does not collect or store any personal information about its visitors and/or users. The system will record your email address and other information if volunteered to us by you, for example via the "Contact Us" page. You do not have to provide personal information if you do not wish to. We do not collect any personal information using cookies and we will not collect any personal information about you except anonymous data that is required for system administration and statistical analysis. 

Any anonymous data that we collect will be used in the following ways:  
a. To personalize your experience – your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs.  
b. To improve our website – we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.  
c. To improve customer service – your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.  

**Do we use cookies?**   
We do not use cookies.  

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not collect, sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites. 

**Security Measures**

We work hard to protect the security of your information. While we strive to protect your information by using appropriate security measures to protect our system, such security cannot be guaranteed. Consequently, we do not insure or warrant the security of information you transmit, and you do so at your own risk.

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

**Children & Parents**

We do not offer or provide products and services for children. If you are under 13, you may not use our Site or our Software. We do not intend to collect Personal Information from children. If your child has submitted Personal Information and you would like to request that such information be removed, you may contact us via one of the contact methods described on the Site and we will promptly remove such information and shall not use such information or include it in our database. Users under the age of thirteen and their parents or guardians are advised that any Personal Information voluntarily entered by children may be available for public access until becomes aware that a user is under the age of thirteen and has had a reasonable opportunity to remove the information from our storage areas.

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Terms & Conditions**

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at [Terms of Service](http://www.chatvibes.com/tos.html).

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our website’s privacy policy. 

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**  
We may change this Privacy Policy from time-to-time. If we do make a change, we will post the revised Privacy Policy on this Site. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy periodically. Questions, comments or complaints about our privacy policies should be submitted to us via the methods described on the Site. 

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us via email: info@chatvibes.com
